<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://theme481-wedding.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme481-wedding.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://theme481-wedding.myshopify.com/blogs/news/tagged/dresses-for-her.atom"/>
  <title>Perfect Bride - Blog</title>
  <updated>2018-10-11T00:42:00-12:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Perfect Bride</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme481-wedding.myshopify.com/blogs/news/the-assortment-of-our-wedding-store-will-glad-your-eyes-and-help-you-get-everything-you-need-for-this-special-day</id>
    <published>2018-10-11T00:41:00-12:00</published>
    <updated>2018-10-11T00:41:00-12:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme481-wedding.myshopify.com/blogs/news/the-assortment-of-our-wedding-store-will-glad-your-eyes-and-help-you-get-everything-you-need-for-this-special-day"/>
    <title>The assortment of our wedding store will glad your eyes and help you get everything you need for this special day</title>
    <author>
      <name>Your Wife</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong>When you ask a woman about the most memorable days of her life, she will certainly mention her wedding day in a list of others</strong></p>
<p>When you ask a woman about the most memorable days of her life, she will certainly mention her wedding day in a list of others. Of course, she remembers the first time she met her future husband on the wonderful May day, but the day that happened in a year, the wedding one, will always stay apart in her reminiscences along with the birth of her children and the time she fell in love with their father.</p>
<ul>
<li>Dresses for her</li>
<li>Suits for him</li>
<li>Accessories for her</li>
<li>Accessories for him</li>
<li>Card Invitations</li>
</ul>
<p>So many pleasant moments filled her life before it, so many preparations where done before it. And at last it happened, the most wonderful, charming and so welcome day at the ocean margin. She remembers the sunny weather, the murmuring breakers, the love in his eyes, her elated mood, happiness, the beautiful streaming dress, the modest suit of the ever loved person close to her. There are so many such stories, so different at each particular case, but always inspiring and evoking smiles, pleasant emotions and lighting the eyes.</p>
<p>Making your special days even more special, we feel happier. Our goal is to make you feel not so absorbed with all the difficulties that deal with the usual preparations, and to provide you with all the high-level services. We try our best to solve any problems that arise in the process of preparations, offer you the goods you need and support with everything.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
